B: Hey.
I: Hey, Ben.
Are you OK?
B: I’m fine.
Let’s go.
I: Have you warmed up yet?
M: I can help you stretch if you like.
Warming up is very important.
I: Yes.
Max has some great ideas for warming up.
B: Yeah, I saw them.
Thanks, Max.
I’m OK.
I’ve warmed up.
I ran here.
Let’s go.
I: Ben? What’s wrong?
B: Just uhh… out of breath…
M: OK.
Take a break.
Here.
It’s important to drink water when you’re exercising.
B: It’s cool.
I’m OK now.
Come on.
M: Maybe slow down a bit, Ben?
B: Don’t worry about me.
I’m fine.
I: Huh.
A text from Carla.
‘Hi, Izzy.
Ben’s not answering his texts.
How’s his back? He went home from work early.’
What’s the matter with your back?
B: It’s nothing serious.
I: Nothing serious?
Look at you.
B: OK, I hurt it this morning, moving heavy boxes.
I: Why didn’t you tell me when I called?
Why did you run with a bad back?
B: Look, I thought I was OK.
I took some ibuprofen.
I: Why did you run so fast?
You and Max were running like it was the Olympics.
B: I don’t know what you mean.
I: You were being silly, both of you,
but especially you, with a bad back.
B: Look, I feel fine.
What time is it?
I: It’s six.